dvs HIBS: XOCECE Q RARE
de $B: XOCECE Q statis let me ask you iLEAliR
oS nat if told you that just 1 hour MRRARMSARS Lat
SPE nat ifl told you that just 1 hour MRRARMBARS Lat
due HGS: XOCECE aleae 60 minutes 605354
de HGS: XOCECE Olean 60 minutes 605354
could completely change the direction of your life mee onmaxceeniy tt 757 Tal de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
could completely change the direction of your life mae onmaxceeniy tt 757 [al dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
would you believe me SBS dus FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
das 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
most people won't KEBAFE de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
why because ie been solda le AHA, BvthiRee 7 its dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
why because he been solda le AHA, BvthiRee 7 Vit BS de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they think transformation needs a miracle Hote DS Fe Se By dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
they think transformation needs a miracle Hie DS Fe SF de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
they think transformation needs a miracle Hoi Fe DS Fe SF dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they think Success demands 2 0 hour days HOTTA A RID BSR 20/84 dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they think Success demands 2 0 hour days HOTA A RID BSR 20/8 ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
luck orasilver spoon semi et dns 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
luck ora silver spoon semi met de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but I'm here to tell you it doesn't RESINS TEAR de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
but I'm here to tell you it doesn't ORES KINX TEA dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it starts with 1 hour just one EAL, RAVI, dus BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it starts with 1 hour just one EAL, RAV). owe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it starts with 1 hour just one EMLpaA, RA—V)VET. dus FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
1 hour of intention one hour of discipline Linnea Lipase dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
1 hour of intention one hour of discipline Lisnaa Lipase de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
1 hour of intention one hour of discipline Linnea Late dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour where you decide to work on you —w AY, ree Rot FE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour where you decide to work on you —w AY, mee Rot FE dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
instead of watching someone else live their life mASB ea tt IG de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
instead of watching someone else live their life mASB ea Ate dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
see most people are busy but very few are growing B, KSMAMRIL, ARDEA RK (etd 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
see most people are busy but very few are growing B, KSMARRIL, ARDEA RK des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
see most people are busy but very few are growing B, KSMAMRIL, ARDEA RK dus FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
see most people are busy but very few are growing B, KSMAMRIL, ARDEA RK dvs FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
they scroll they rush they repeat HHT, HTC, tees de 44BS: XOCECE Q RAR
they Scroll they rush they repeat HHT, ATIC, tees dvs #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but they don't stop and they don't think enninate BK, reas de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
but they don't stop and they don't think enninate PK, reas dae 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but they don't stop and they don't think eqns PK, reas de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and because they don't think they don't change HAMMAR ARSE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and because they don't think they don't change BAHAR ARSENE dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but you if you're still listening you're different EMRE, MRT dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but you if you're still listening you're different AEMRIMAEM, HAT (etd 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but you if you're still listening you're different AEMRIMAEM, HRA T dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you're Searching you're ready UTE BARNES FT de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're Searching you're ready UTE BARES ET dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and today we're going to talk about the hour SRBMRIRAAT de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and today we're going to talk about the hour SRBMRIR AAT des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that can reshape your habits AB Bey 1h de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
that can reshape your habits AB Bey 1h dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
your income PRET de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
your relationships and yes even your legacy MOR FA, BAN, SE MeO dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
your relationships and yes even your legacy MOR FA, BAN, SE MeO dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
your relationships and yes even your legacy MOR FA, BAN, BE MeOH dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because SUCCESS is NOt an accident mA Ree dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because SUCCESS is NOt an accident mA ABBR dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's a daily decision RBSRVRE dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part you don't need a New Year RENE aE dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part you don't need a New Year RENE ee aE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part you don't need a New Year RENE eae owe $485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need permission PRB B AT de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and you don't need a big break MPREEAS dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and you don't need a big break RPREEAS dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
all you need is one hour a day MABRSR— ot dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
all you need is one hour a day MABRSA— at dus F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
let's begin bse Fane owe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
take back the first hour we SB — at dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
take back the first hour we SB — a dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
let me tell you something powerful ib SRABY AR dwe #45: XOCECE Q RAR
how you Start your day ARS FE EARS — de F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
how you Start your day AROO FESR — dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
determines how you live your life een Eh de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
determines how you live your life een Eh dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not just a routine it's a ritual RARLERGAR, R—AMyyst dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not just a routine it's a ritual RAMLEAGAR, xB—Ayyst des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not just a routine it's a ritual RAMLEAGAR, xB—Ayyst dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and that first hour Bet dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
that's your window your launchpad your foundation REMAP, (NAHE, HAVE, dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's your window your launchpad your foundation REMAP, (NAA, HAVE, de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's your window your launchpad your foundation PEMNEP, (BAA, HAVE, de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
now most people they give it away MEKSMAMIBERAT dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now most people they give it away WEKSMAMIBERAT de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
now most people they give it away WEKSMAMIBERAT dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they wake up and they reach for the phone TER, Re BIE de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they wake up and they reach for the phone OTE, Re BIE des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they check messages they check the news HIB HS, this eee de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
they check messages they check the news HIS HS, this eee) dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they check messages they check the news HN HS, thie) dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they check what everyone else is doing eA sete A ett dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they check what everyone else is doing eed ES sete A ett de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but what they don't check is themselves eH ewes dvs BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but what they don't check is themselves eH we was de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they don't ask what do! want today tHiTRSRS KBE tA dss #45: XOCECE Q RARE
they don't ask what do! want today HHTRaRS RBBTA de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
they don't ask what do! want today HTRSRS RBBITA ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what do | need to become what am | building REBMATA? REBEtA? de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what do | need to become what am | building REBMAtA? REBEtA? dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you see KE (eetl #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you don't program your mind in the first hour mRNA A SE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
if you don't program your mind in the first hour RIES he A aE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
the world will do it for you Th Ravtnnes dws 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
the world will do it for you TE Rasotnenes de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and let me Warn you dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
doesn't always have your best interests in mind HARBIN Bll iw EE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
doesn't always have your best interests in mind HRS Bll i EE dws 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
doesn't always have your best interests in mind HARB Bll im EE dus 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it'll feed you drama distraction noise Cae El Eres dove FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it'll feed you drama distraction noise ere cr S84 Veda a=) de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it'll feed you drama distraction noise Cae A Eres owe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and before you know it EMBRZ a de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and before you know it EMBRE Za dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're reacting to life instead of designing it ones Ei RM MARBILITE de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
you're reacting to life instead of designing it ones e Ei RM MABILIT S dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you're reacting to life instead of designing it oneent EE MAILS de $483: XOCECE Q RARE
so here's the challenge me Pb ay dwe $483: XOCECE Q RAR
take back that first hour ESRD H— Mat de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
take back that first hour BSR MH— Mat dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
make it yours SEEAR TI ene de #45: XOCECE Q RAR
before the emails EF MZ aT dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
before the Scrolling before the chaos ERonZ ELSA de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
before the Scrolling before the chaos RS ELLA ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
before the Scrolling before the chaos RZ ELTA dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
get up alittle earlier REF—A dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
not because it's trendy dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not because it's trendy dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but because it's transformational meaner Ss StH de #483: XOCECE Q RARE
but because it's transformational meaner Ss StH dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and use that hour to build you FAX RITE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and use that hour to build you FAX RITE dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
read 10 pages ofa good book mon eB de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
read 10 pages of a good book mon eB dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
write down three things you're grateful for STReRH= te de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
write down three things you're grateful for STReRH= te dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
plan your day ea comed de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
visualize your goals move your body drink water sasiney ATS DH one BF (owk dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
visualize your goals move your body drink water sasuinty ATS DH one BF (Bork dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
visualize your goals move your body drink water sasinty An FS DN ot (Bow rk dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
visualize your goals move your body drink water sagen BATS DH och BF (ow k de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
sit in silence Be dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
do what the old you never made time for fier Made BY [Bs] eo de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
do what the old you never made time for fier Made BY [a dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's the truth make SS dus BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's the truth make BS dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
my friend RNR dus FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
if you can Win the first hour you can Win the day RIMES SBM et, enataeie tS dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you can Win the first hour you can Win the day URES SBM et, emataei tS de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you can Win the first hour you can Win the day URES SBM et, emataeie tS dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you win enough days you win your life mRimeT ees AF, tamey ny 7 done #45: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you win enough days you win your life mR T EBSHAF, mRmeT ny 7 dwe #BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you win enough days you win your life mR T EBSHAF, metmeT ny 7 dns #85: XOCECE Q RARE
now! know what some people say dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
I'm nota morning person RRETRENA de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
but listen success doesn't Care ena h BE dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
but listen success doesn't Care eneRIxh BE de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but listen Success doesn't Care ene Rie h BE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
discipline doesn't ask how you feel HEPA MR My de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
discipline doesn't ask how you feel HPA MR Ma] dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
you think the WiNNEFS of this world leap out of bed nin ras TE FR AY am BRS MRE wR de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you think the WiNNEFS of this world leap out of bed dria ras TE FR AY ian BRS MRE wR des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
with fireworks and fanfare man A SDR ER de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
with fireworks and fanfare ean A SDR ER due 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
NO they decide A, tei TRE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they train they build the habit and so can you HHT, ATE AR SDR, other TL dwe 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
they train they build the habit and so can you HAT, HUTTE AR SIR, otbaTeL. de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they train they build the habit and so can you HAT, HUTTE AR SDR, otbaTTL. dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they train they build the habit and so can you HAT, ANTE AR SIR, otbaTTL. de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so Starting tomorrow make a new deal with yourself PROUMIB RAS, HHS CNN SC des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so Starting tomorrow makea new deal with yourself PROUMBB RAS, HH CNN SC de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so Starting tomorrow makea new deal with yourself PROUMBB RAS, HH CNN SC de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
before you touch the world touch your future eimai ae oi AFS RAK de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
before you touch the world touch your future eimai a ATS RAK owe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
use that first hour not to consume but to create AS inireweme wis dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
use that first hour not to consume but to create Ash inire wee wis de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
use that first hour not to consume but to create AS Pinna weme wis dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
don't just wake up FERS de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
rise Up because your future isn't waiting atllam IR, HAMMARTAE LLL AS ci dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
rise Up because your future isn't waiting atllam IR, HAMMARTAE LLL AS ici de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
rise Up because your future isn't waiting atllam IR, HAMMARTAE LLL AS ici dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
rise Up because your future isn't waiting atllam IR, HAMMARTAE LLL AS ici de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's waiting at 6 cHOmees owe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so take it back pr low de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
build it strong eRe dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and when the day begins YX FRA EHR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and when the day begins RFA EHR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll already be ahead MEBBRAET de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
mentally spiritually and emotionally mala LAE des BS: XOCECE Q RARE
mentally spiritually and emotionally we Lie LAL de 4B S: XOCECE OQ RARE
mentally spiritually and emotionally we Lie LAL dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
you won't just be pre ared you'll be powertul AE APES EEE A de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you won't just be pre ared you'll be powerful MAES EEE A dwe 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
you won't just be pre ared you'll be powerful MAE APES EEE A dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that is how the — transformation begins mete DFT dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and that is how the — transformation begins mete DFT de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
guard the hour like treasure SF Atmos de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
guard the hour like treasure SF Ati dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now that you've taken back the first hour BRPMRILLT 58 —M it de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now that you've taken back the first hour BRPMMILELT 58 —t it dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
the next step is to guard it like treasure F-SRE RTE ETRE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
the next step is to guard it like treasure FSET EASE dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
the next step is to guard it like treasure F-SRERTE ESRC dvs FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because let me tell you people will try to Steal it RALKSRRANSRe Ge dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because let me tell you people will try to Steal it AALRSRRANSRea Ge de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because let me tell you people will try to steal it AALRSRRANSRa Ge ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not with a SUN but with a notification a favor Fen, meee etl de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
not with a SUN but with a notification a favor Fen, mee BIC dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
not with a SUN but with a notification a favor Fen, mee BIC de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
ameaningless task BEBE S dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
ameaningless task BERLIOS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
alittle hey can | just BOR, RBERGE due F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
alittle hey can | just BmOR, RBERGE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and suddenly your hour's gone my MIST dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and suddenly your hour's gone omens Bs RIS T dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and suddenly your hour's gone omens BT RIS T dae 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
vanished given away to _ something that builds their life WaT, maT en one de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
vanished given away to _ something that builds their life WaT, maT en hone dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
vanished given away to _ something that builds their life WaT, maT en home dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
not yours RET dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you've got to understand this our is not free (ra — Ae He By de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to understand this our is not free EA — Re He BH des #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to understand this our is not free EA — Re He BH dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not casual RE ERY dwe F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not casual REE de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not for leftovers wee RSH dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
it's not for leftovers wee RSH de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
itis Sacred itis strategic ceven, CEakbgeny dwe 4S: XOCECE OQ RARE
itis Sacred itis strategic ceven, Ceakbgteny de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and if you don't protect it son RIPE dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
no one else will HhARRE dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you see time is like money met Alma & dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you see time is like money melt Almak de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
but even more dangerous to lose eeAB IE iO dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but even more dangerous to lose eeAB ie iy de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can always earn another dollar SRS BERS ME FETC ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can always earn another dollar IRE BERS LE ETC de 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but you'll never get back that hour mae RAT dae #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
but you'll never get back that hour mae RAT dss #483: XOCECE Q RARE
so what do we do BETZ EAD? owe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
we put upa fence supae 7 HE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
we say this is my hour ailmxenclt Zl) dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
we say this is my hour ailxenclt 2) de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
no calls no emails no scrolling no distractions RABI, eae: RAR, BA my ds HS: XOCECE Q RARE
no calls no emails no scrolling no distractions RABE, ear, BARN, RA my de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
no calls no emails no scrolling no distractions RABE, ear: BARN, RA my de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
no calls no emails no scrolling no distractions RABE, ear: BARN, RA my de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not because we're rude but because we're S€rlous FERRARI MEnERARN2 Aw dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not because we're rude but because we're S€rlous FRRARIMEnERARN2I\ Aw de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to get Serious about your hour igi Box tne BY |] dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to get Serious about your hour eras sorts trey BY [eB] dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to get Serious about your hour ena sorts trey BY [eB] dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
like a builder is Serious about his tools RR—TEALAM HALA RUA de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
like a builder is Serious about his tools R—TEALAM HALA RUA dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
like a farmer BTR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
is S@riOUS about his Soil sath cb Sth dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
is S@riOUS about his Soil sabes Ste dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because this hour if you use it right ask Mhatase din FA xt dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because this hour if you use it right sak atense dn FA Rt dus 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
because this hour if you use it right BAe AIT ST dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
will pay you backa hundredfold in clarity aaxnliRin—B te de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
will pay you backa hundredfold in clarity aaxuliR(n— Ble dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
in Skillin results inincomein confidence TERRELL, MAL, Eiadt de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
in Skillin results inincomein confidence TERRELL, MAL, Efadbt ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
in Skillin results inincomein confidence TERRELL, MAL, Hfadbt dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
in Skillin results inincomein confidence TERRELL, MAL, Hfadbt des 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but only if you don't trade it for crumbs enRenrsen hl LS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but only if you don't trade it for crumbs emeenreer iH LS des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
let me Say that again ILRI dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
don't trade gold for crumbs FERRER dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
don't trade gold for crumbs FERRERO dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's what people do when they say SAV dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's what people do when they say SAV dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
I'll just check this one thing pane—ft SB dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
I'll just check this one thing pRea—ffS de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
let me reply real quick ULRRREZ. dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
this won't take long RSE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
this won't take long RASTER ALE dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and they end up spending their best hour Hath 7 RA et dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
reacting to the world st TE FR tet 2B dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
reacting to the world so TE FR tet BZ BY de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
instead of rebuilding their world mReE emote FR dwe F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
instead of rebuilding their world mreE emt FR dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so here's the habit sme RAS) dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
every night schedule your hour label it set it in stone SRBLRMONNITS, COEae BAL dss #5: XOCECE Q RARE
every night schedule your hour label it set it in stone SRBLRMONITS, CEaE BAL dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
every night schedule your hour label it set it in stone SRBLROINITS, CEae BAL dss #45: XOCECE Q RARE
every night schedule your hour label it set it in stone SRBLROINITS, Eee BALE dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
no flexibility no negotiations RARBERARA de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
no flexibility no negotiations RARBERARA dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
tell your family your friends even yourself AMORA ARES SME ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
tell your family your friends even yourself AMORA ARESSME dvs F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
tell your family your friends even yourself AMORA MARES SME dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
tell your family your friends even yourself AMORA ARES SME des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
this is your time to grow to think to create to build EMMA, BS, ONiS, IL de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
this is your time to grow to think to create to build EMH, BS, iS, BIL dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
this is your time to grow to think to create to build AMMAR, BS, iS, BIT due 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
this is your time to grow to think to create to build EMMMKHER, BS, iS, BIL dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and if they don't respect it teach them to MRHIFSHE, Mate dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if they don't respect it teach them to MRHIFSHE, Meo dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not with anger but with consistency aememetesw— de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not with anger but with consistency owe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not with anger but with consistency de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because when you value your time mands te AY IE) Bt dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
because when you value your time waynes te AY IE) Bt de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
people begin to value you Me UR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so the rule is simple PR DU eee dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so the rule is simple PRU eee dws #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if it doesn't ZFOW you it doesn't get your hour period MREFILMMEK, CRRA MRA) ET ARE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if it doesn't ZFOW you it doesn't get your hour period MREFILMMEK, CRRA MAYES ARE dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if it doesn't ZFOW you it doesn't get your hour period MREPILMMEK, CRRA MAYES ARE dus 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
this isn't just about productivity xan AA ala dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
this isn't just about productivity sore Niele de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about priority xext (i ttehey dwe 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about priority xext i ttehe de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about saying my future matters enough to defend it mevanaE LE De dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about saying my future matters enough to defend it mevanaEe LE De de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and that first hour that's your frontline SB hate enya dss 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
and that first hour that's your frontline SB hate enya ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
so gUard it like it's rare because itis PURE RRPE, ANE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so gUaIC it like it's rare because itis PURE RPE, ANE dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so ZUaIC it like it's rare because itis PURE RPE, ANSE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's the hour that Separates the average xeon FLY (Bava dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's the hour that Separates the average xeon FLY (Bava de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
from the excellent MB dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the wanderer from the leader the talker from the doer RS HomascrRVsKs de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the wanderer from the leader the talker from the doer RSF owmascrRVsKs dws 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
the wanderer from the leader the talker from the doer RSA owmascrRVsKs dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you guard it today you'll celebrate it tomorrow MRSRHECS, MARRS RME dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you guard it today you'll celebrate it tomorrow MRISKHEC, MRM RME de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and if you guard it today you'll celebrate it tomorrow MRISKHEC, MRM RME dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
$485: XOCECE Q RARE
direction before action TAHA dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
direction before action THAN A de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you know it's NOt enough to take the hour PRATER EY dss 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you know it's NOt enough to take the hour PRATER EY de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and it's not enough to guard it saree dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and it's not enough to guard it saree dus 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
you've gotta know what to do with It (nee GARE dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you've gotta know what to do with It nee GARE dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's where most people go wrong REASsHAM ENA owe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's where most people go wrong meAseA WRIA de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
they're active Hei FEER dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they're busy they're doing things lots of things THITRIC, (HITE MRS BH. due #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they're busy they're doing things lots of things HHITRIC, (HITE MRS BH. dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they're busy they're doing things lots of things HHITRIC, (HITTERS BH. dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but the question is lal aie dvs #485: XOCECE Q RARE
are they doing the right things oft LE BABY SS tes 092 de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
are they doing the right things s(t ER LE BABY SS tes 032 dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
because here's the RARE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's the RARE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
action without direction isa recipe for frustration we Platt ap wine de FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
action without direction isa recipe for frustration Be la Taian dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
action without direction isa recipe for frustration Be aT alain de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's like being ona treadmill RREBS ML dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
sweating grinding running but going nowhere FTUR ES, seam, wee de BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
sweating grinding running but going nowhere FRR, eee, sees dwe 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
sweating grinding running but going nowhere FRR, eee, seas de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
so before you jUMP into your hour PROTEASE Za de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so before you jUMP into your hour PRUE Ae LEZ at dus 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
before you dive into books before you Start building TERA BAS Z AUTEN SZ a ds 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
before you dive into books before you Start building TERA BAS Z AUTEN SZ de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
before you dive into books before you Start building TERA BAS Z AUTEM BS Za des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
before you dive into books before you Start building TERA BAS Z AUTEN BS Za ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
before you hit play ona video FRR EEK Bt dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
for the last week +A de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
for the last week +A owe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
cryptocurrencies have been in a free fall meses we de rT Coinbase: B fH: xoceCE , - Install Q RetaE
cryptocurrencies have been in afree fall meas ae dss rT Coinbase: Buy BT... ABS: XOCECE ” F uy Install Q Reta
giving Concern to investors around the world is LEAS MRA SS dss rT Coinbase: Buy BT... Cd aise ” F uy Install Q Reta
giving Concern to investors around the world is {LHR SMNRABRES Skip >I dss rT Coinbase: Buy BT... ec ” . ay, Install Q Reta
giving Concern to investors around the world is {LHAS MNRAS ES Skip >I dss rT Coinbase: Buy BT... Lees ” . ay, Install Q Reta
ask yourself a very powerful question aaa—Mes a 77 nial dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
ask yourself a very powerful question aso—Mes a 7) nial de #45: XOCECE Q RAR
ask yourself a very powerful question aso—Mes a 77 nile dws #485: XOCECE Q RAR
where am | going REAMZ? dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
that question unlocks everything xvas ia S—Y) dwe 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
that question unlocks everything xtaeFt aS —) dss 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
because if you don't have direction BAR Fl dss HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because if you don't have direction BARI FTA de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you won't have progress inner Ht ay dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll MOVE but you won't arrive BHA, eineshs dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll MOVE but you won't arrive BHA, inResbs dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll MOVE but you won't arrive BHA, iresbs dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
direction is the compass aaetara it de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
#485: XOCECE Q RARE
action is the engine and you need both THES |S, mmsawe des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
action is the engine and you need both THES |S, mmsawe de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so let's get practical PROLLRTSE PRR dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so let's get practical PROLLERTSE BR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
at the Start of your hour FERS FBT dwe 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
take three minutes just three to get clear HED RED thames de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
take three minutes just three to get clear KEP RED hams dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
take three minutes just three to get clear KEP RED thaws de #483: XOCECE Q RARE
ask yourself what's my goal AAS CRN AREA dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
ask yourself what's my goal FAB CRN AREA dss 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
what's the Skill I'm building REGIA AERA? dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what's the Skill I'm building REMAOIRAERHA? de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what am | trying to improve today RS RRMA? dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what am I trying to improve today RS RRMA? dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and most important why does it matter tome REEVE, AtaRitHiRBE? dws 4B S: XOCECE OQ RARE
and most important why does it matter tome REEVE, AtaRtRBE? de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and most important why does it matter tome REEVE, AtaxitRBE? dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
write it down SER de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
don't keep it in your head BN BicteheF 2 dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
get it on paper poset de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
getit on paper poset dove #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because Clarity on paper becomes focus in action mn2 Leno 1T oh de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because Clarity on paper becomes focus in action mnZ Lemont Topo dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
Jim Roone used to say reasons come first Jim Roone*# st mEs— de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
Jim Roone used to say reasons come first Jim Roone# ims — dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
Jim Roone used to say reasons come first Jim Roone# it mEs— due #485: XOCECE Q RARE
answers come second SRA dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
answers come second SRHHER A de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to know your reason because when you do ballad Hare Sense ey ET dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to know your reason because when you do THT BEE 7a Senay at dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the rest becomes Obvious AT HREMART dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
the rest becomes Obvious RT HRLMART dvs 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
now let me give you a warning mre SS dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now let me give you a warning mien SS dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you Skip this step WRB — dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
ifyou jump straight to action without intention meine BERETA de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
ifyou jump straight to action without intention meme BR KA TA owe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
ifyou jump straight to action without intention meme BR KA TA de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
you'll waste the most precious resource you've got traik Bein Se bas dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll waste the most precious resource you've got mraiR Bein Se bays de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
your fOCUS and here's what's worse PUEBLA dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
your fOCUS and here's what's worse PUERAC SN dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
your fOCcUS and here's what's worse PUERACS SN dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll Confuse movement with meaning oeeaan (Fame SC dus 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll Confuse movement with meaning maaan (Fame SC dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll feel productive but you'll stay stuck REWER RR, MSR AE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll feel productive but you'll stay stuck MEMRAM, MSR AE ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll feel productive but you'll stay stuck MEMRAM, MSR AE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's why direction matters more than Speed SMEAR a eee de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's why direction matters more than Speed RMENHA AIRE eee dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because it doesn't matter how fast you're gOINg. RARE HASR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because it doesn't matter how fast you're gOINg RARE HASR due #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because it doesn't matter how fast you're gOINg RARE HASR dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're going the wrong Way since fe S BS de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so take the time to aim pvkve AY [El mae dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
so take the time to aim privé AS [A mae dus #485: XOCECE Q RAR
take the time to ask FERAL alA] dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
take the time to ask FERAL ALAl de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
take the time to align your actions with your outcomes FeMiaL neo {TANS anes BR Re dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
take the time to align your actions with your outcomes TeMiaL neo {TANS ene aR Rte dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
take the time to align your actions with your outcomes FeMiaL ene {TADS eae aR Rte dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because a Man with direction he walks slower Bata lb Ace Ete ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because a Man with direction he walks slower Bata lb Ace ete de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but he gets further (A ihiES Biz de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
but he gets further (BHhES Biz dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so tomorrow morning when your hour begins PROBA SL ineoasiarrr enya de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so tomorrow morning when your hour begins PROBA _L itneoasiarrsnoas ia ds F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
don't just Start doing de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
don't just Start doing dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
start deciding Frere de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
decide who you want to become seen RB AAI HE dws #485: XOCECE Q RAR
decide who you want to become seen AB AAI E de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
decide what matters most des 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
decide what matters most dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
decide what step rem — dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
brings you Closer to the life you' ve been dreaming of ibinoeiese SAB Ary 3h ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
brings you Closer to the life you' ve been dreaming of ibinpeiese FAB Pay t 5 due FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because direction turns your hour into a mission wa emo By alse s ESS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because direction turns your hour into a mission wa emo By elses ES dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
because direction turns your hour into a mission way emo By elses ES de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
and when you live with mission wants a on E has dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
you start Walking a whole new pat FE LSS AIS BB de $45: XOCECE Q RAR
you start Walking a whole new pat SRE LSS AIS BR due 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
and that path clear focused intentional xem Mit, sanz dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and that path clear focused intentional xem Mit, sanz dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that path clear focused intentional xqum iM Pit, sanz dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
is the one that leads to change 2S Enmt dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
is the one that leads to change 2S S nwt de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
learn for an hour grow fora lifetime — ies, —EF ARE de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
learn for an hour grow fora lifetime — es, —EF ARE des 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
learn for an hour grow fora lifetime — ie, —E FARE de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
if there's one thin I've Learned in life MRRBREFSFIT ta dwe 44H S: XOCECE Q RAR
if there's one thin I've Learned in life MRURAEF FST (ta dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's SUCCESS doesn't just come from doing mapa BF SER due #485: XOCECE Q RAR
it's SUCCESS doesn't just come from doing mA BF SER de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's SUCCESS doesn't just come from doing mar BF ER dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it comes from Sse what to O ORAS S Seta de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it comes from come what to fe) ORAT SS wata dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the moment you Stop learning you stop growing wens sane, dmenfeElLl T ARAL de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the moment you stop learning you stop growing wens sane, menfEll T ARAL ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the moment you Stop learning you stop growing wens sane, enfElLl T ARAL dus 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now here's the good news dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now here's the good news de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
learning is simple FRB dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's not about it going back to are Rolla de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not about eOIne back to are FR dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not about expensive programs SRR AX de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not about expensive programs xS5RROIM AEX dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about Setting aside just one focused hour a day xextS RRS tee de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about Setting aside just one focused hour a day xextS RRS dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about Setting aside just one focused hour a day xext SRR test de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's about Setting aside just one focused hour a day xext SRR test dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
to feed your mind PEM BR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that hour that's your edge wena dwe #45: XOCECE Q RAR
that hour that's your edge wees de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
that's your secret weapon BBE A Bes dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
that's your Secret weapon wine ES Bes de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because when most people are watching nonsense RASAS HA ME BRIS wE des #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because when most people are watching nonsense RASAS HA ME BRS WER dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you're watching growth onesie BAR dws BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're watching growth onesie BAR dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
when they're drifting Ee Srl dws 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're developing ERR de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and over time day by day MBA, —AY—K dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and over time day by day RBA, —AY—K de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that learning starts to separate you from the crowd FS ABIRMA Bech 5} Ps LK dws #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that learning starts to separate you from the crowd FABIMRMA ech 5} Bs LK dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
JiM Roone said at best His Sa Buss dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
Jim Roone said at best de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
formal education will make youa living TERlaasitinte dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
formal education will make youa living TERlaesinimte de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
self education will make you a fortune BRAB sine dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
self education will make youa fortune BRAB sine de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
self education will make you a fortune BRAB sine dwe #483: XOCECE Q RAR
so what do you learn during that hour BANE I BFS TA? dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so what do you learn during that hour BANE I BFS TA? ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you read books you listen to mentors you study success Ink, ORS, BILAL. de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you read books you listen to mentors you study success nik, ORS, DFT ARID. des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you read books you listen to mentors you study success Ink, ORS, BFL ARID. dus 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you read books you listen to mentors you study success erik, HORS, MB FL ARID. dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you pick up biographies personal development MRICS ARR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you pick up biographies personal development MBRRICTARR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you pick up biographies personal development MBRRICTARR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
communication health wealth mindset mace TB DAs dss BS: XOCECE Q RARE
communication health wealth mindset mace TB As de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
communication health wealth mindset mace TB DAs ds FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
the stuff that moves the needle Bahn de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
the stuff that moves the needle Baha dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because the More you learn the more you see BAER RS, oe SIR ws de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because the More you learn the more you see BA FE RS, oe SIR ws dwe #43: XOCECE Q RARE
because the More you learn the more you see BAF RS, oe BIR ws de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and the More you see the better choices you make PB SAIGS , MMM AERA des 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the MOFre you see the better choices you make PB SIES , MMM AEB dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the More you see the better choices you make PB SAIES , (MM AEB de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
now let me be Clear MELB dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
this isn't passive eae ann dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
you're not just Scrolling quotes MP RBERHS|S de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you're not just scrolling quotes MPRBERHS|S dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and hoping something sticks wae RB aeatt de BS: XOCECE Q RAR
you're intentional dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you pick up the book Ret de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you pick up the book ees dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the course The Notebook on purpose BRN SIOAR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
the course The Notebook on purpose MENSA des FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
the course The Notebook on purpose MENSA dus FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and you say this is my growth hour onesceeeny PSE des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and you say this is my growth hour enpesceseey PRET St de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and let me tell you an hour a day adds up in one year iLRe, —R— ese ds BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and let me tell you an hour a day adds up in one year iene, —K— havmeeeae— de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and let me tell you an hour a day adds up in one year LRA, —R— ese ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and let me tell you an hour a day adds up in one year besa, —K— hevmeeeae— de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's 365 hours BBRRESOS et dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's 365 hours BBRRESOS et de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's more than nine full time work weeks guvomnSEn Le dvs 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's more than nine full time work weeks muomn SEA Le de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
invested in yourown mind KRAsnean Bie dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
invested in yourown mind KRAtnaaw Bie de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you do that for a year PRE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you do that for a year PRE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and you won't even recognize yourself ezeilRi Bor dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and you won't even recognize yourself mezeail Ri Bor de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
your language improves neve BE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
your confidence rises ements de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
your confidence rises ements dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you speak with Clarity ont {RIB ee de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you think Sharper ota se dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you solve problems that used to Stop you cold ARB T sata Lon FO we de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you solve problems that used to Stop you cold RRR T sata btn FO we dws 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you solve problems that used to Stop you cold ARR T Stas LL On FO we (etl #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
why because you've been stacking wisdom bit by bit Ata? BAth-Be AT RS des #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
why because you've been stacking wisdom bit by bit Ata? BAth—-Be As RS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
why because you've been stacking wisdom bit by bit Ata? BAth—Be AT RS dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
why because you've been stacking wisdom bit by bit Ata? BABE As RS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
Page by page lesson by lesson dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
Page by page lesson by lesson de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part nobody can take it away from you RANE RARE MMNSWSE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part nobody can take it away from you RANBRARMEMMBUSE de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part nobody can take it away from you RANBRARMEMMSUSE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
skills can be Learned geen LS Se de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence can be built knowledge multiplies eT IZ AIA eS dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
confidence can be built knowledge multiplies ede IZ AIA BS de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence can be built knowledge multiplies ede IZ AIA eS dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and it all begins with that one quiet hour xan re RA) VET de HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and it all begins with that one quiet hour xen VET dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and it all begins with that one quiet hour xe re RAVES de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so here's your next step PRUE URRY BE dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
pick your materials before your hour begins etn — at Fem AIZE RA AA AL de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
pick your materials before your hour begins etn — at Fram AL owe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
pick your materials before your hour begins etn — at Fram AIZE RA AA AL de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
don't leave it to chance Fee RAMs dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
stack three books on your desk cue up the podcast HEAPRERT LTS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
stack three books on your desk cue up the podcast HEAPRERT LATS dss BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
stack three books on your desk cue up the podcast HEAPRERF LATS de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
stack three books on your desk cue up the podcast HEAPRERT LTS des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
open the Course you've been putting off FTF BRIE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
open the Course you've been putting off FTF RB IRE dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and when that hour starts go in deep YB) BFR dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and when that hour starts go in deep SAB SFR de F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because every time you open your mind BAS RAL FE DBE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because every time you open your mind BASRA FE DY BE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you expand your future nth RB otk de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you expand your future nth RB otk dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the Man or Woman who learns daily earns continually BRFINSARKA THRE de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the Man or Woman who learns daily earns continually BRFINSARKA FGM dvs 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the Man or Woman who learns daily earns continually BRFINSARKA FGM ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so don't skip this PRU BRT dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so don't skip this PRU BRT due FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
don't rush this WBS dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
make learning a habit eee) ti de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and you'll make SUCCeSS a lifestyle ineibetoomen ae HAT dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and you'll make SUCCe€SS a lifestyle ineiketoomen—a HAS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
das 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory atest BIC hat de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory atest BIC + hat dss BS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory atest BIC + hat de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory atest ERIC + at des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
let's get something straight INE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
learning is powerful syetaAw dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
learning is powerful syetaAw de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but learning without doing is just entertainment exmanRe eR dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
but learning without doing is just entertainment exmaHRee AR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but learning without doing is just entertainment exmaHRee AR due #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you canread every book IRE LARS — ANB de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
watch every video listen to every podcast as Mitineves dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
watch every video listen to every podcast as Mitine ves de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
watch every video listen to every podcast as Mitine ves owe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but if you never apply what you' ve Learne fase tn ARF LA dns 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
but if you never apply what you' ve Learne fase tn LA de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you're not growing PRR RS due 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're just collecting mee se dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
see SUCCESS doesn't come from what you know BCLs nO de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARBG
see SUCCESS doesn't come from what you know PCD AzReak e inOeN dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARBG
see SUCCESS doesn't come from what you know Dees eas) dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it comes from what you practice CRAFTS dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it comes from what you practice CRAFTS ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
let me repeat that ike — I dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
1 hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory Linas abt 1 O.nesanezie dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
1 hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory Linas abit 1 O.nestanesie des #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
1 hour of practice beats 10 hours of theory Linas abit 1 O.nestanesie dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
why because action is where skillis born Ata? BAT opete Aesth FT dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
why because action is where skillis born ate? BATT Ae aewee th de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become a Speaker by reading about speaking nA SSL ORF HATS AI Ri dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become a Speaker by reading about speaking eR SH ARF HIROTA Ri de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become a Speaker by reading about speaking inR SSL RAF RAYS I Bi dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become fit by studying exercise routines incest FS) FR ea FER de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become fit by studying exercise routines incest FS) FR eae FER dvs #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't become fit by studying exercise routines inca FS) FRR eae FER de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't master anything by sitting on the Sidelines FS Meee dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't master anything by sitting on the Sidelines HFS Marea dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't master anything by sitting on the Sidelines HFS Meee ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to Step into the arena inna Fete de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you've got to Step into the arena inn maent Fete IA dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
now here's the mistake most people make REASHMA MAIN IRIR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
now here's the mistake most people make REASHA MAIN IRIE dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they wait until they feel ready Sa HES oT de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they wait until they feel ready dS HES oT dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they wait until they're confident serena fel) ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they wait until they're confident smiTessniTa fel) de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they Wait until it's perfect shi SB SESS de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
but here's the truth BRE dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence doesn't come before action AeRART ITO de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence doesn't come before action ABRART ITE ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence doesn't come before action AeRAAT ITO de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence comes from action aeRretTay ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
confidence comes from action aexetTay de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you practice you get sharper SRM, pew ESF) dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you practice you get sharper SRM, nepewe ESF) dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you try you get better prime, ape ie BOF dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you try you get better prime, mae ie BUF dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you show u p SRM dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you show u p SRM dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you ZrOW UP so what does this mean for your hour UREAT , RO RAIBLIE] ORBITZ? dvs #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you ZfOW UP so what does this mean for your hour PRAT , EAVES tA? dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you grOW UP so what does this mean for your hour PRAT , REAAVET ORB tA? des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it means that at least part of that hour RERBEDA— hat dus BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it means that at least part of that hour RERBEDA— et dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
should be hands on maa de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning to write write something MRE FUSE, sate dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning to write write something meme FUSE, sate dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning to speak practice out loud memes Jing, xBgRS) dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning to speak practice out loud memes Jinig, xBeRS) de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning to speak practice out loud memes Jinig, xBeRS) dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning business build the plan mamEee ea, seit kl) de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning business build the plan mamEeea ea, weit kl) dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
if you're learning business build the plan mamEee aM, weit kl) de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
make the pitch HR dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
take the call PROF BIG de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning design open the software and create meee SiRit, wrest # dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning design open the software and create MRM SiR, wT RHA # de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're learning design open the software and create mReEE SF SiQiT, wR Fea dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
nO more waiting BSF de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
NO more prepping ABE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
just doing dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because repetition is the mother of all skill Anse maZAesS dss BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because repetition is the mother of all skill AnmRemaeZS dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because repetition is the mother of all skill AnmRema ESS des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not perfection repetition RENE ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not perfection repetition RENE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't have to get it right the first time ARDS — Ratios de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't have to get it right the first time me SB — Ratios de 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you just have to get it going ReBil CARE RA de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you just have to get it going ReBil CARE RA dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and then you refine it improve it Polish it aettetke, Bote, thste de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
and then you refine it improve it Polish it dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how professionals are made BWA maar nsee de #HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how professionals are made Bl A Aes dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and here's Something else CANHRA de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and here's Something else CAN HRA dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
when you practice daily your progress becomes visible YR, ongetsh Bo FB] Ol dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
when you practice daily your progress becomes visible YARN, ong sh 2 4F By Ol dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
when you practice daily your progress becomes visible YARN, ong sh 2 4F By Ol dvs BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can feel it draenei 3) due BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can Measure it RATT dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you start to trust yourself mri ad dwe #45: XOCECE Q RAR
you start to trust yourself omits ad de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that trust that's the real win Bahai 2A LEAF dws #45: XOCECE Q RARE
and that trust that's the real win Bahai BALE AAA de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because a person who trusts their own effort BA-MEEBCSABA dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because a person who trusts their own effort RA-MEEBCSABA de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
becomes unstoppable REAR dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
becomes unstoppable REAR dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so here's the challenge sme Db ay dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
take what you Learned yesterday and apply it today EOE REI AR SB de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
take what you Learned yesterday and apply it today Eine REEIO AR SRB dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
take what you Learned yesterday and apply it today Cine REI AR SRB dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
even if it's Messy EDERAL dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
even if it's SMall even if it's awkward BEER, BEE RAM de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
even if it's SMall even if it's awkward BIER, BEE RA ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
even if it's SMall even if it's awkward BEER, BEE RA de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
just Start because doing turns knowledge into power FAIL, BD HREIBRIREe ey 7] dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
just Start because doing turns knowledge into power FIL, RA HREBRIRG A 7) due 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
just Start because doing turns knowledge into power FAI, RD HREBRIR eA 7) SS dwe F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and One hour of bold focused FI—P BARES SE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and One hour of bold focused FIP BT ARES SE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
imperfect action can do more for your life ASEAN Ta ai tnt EES de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
imperfect action can do more for your life ASEAN TaD ai tres EES dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
imperfect action can do more for your life ASEAN TaD ai tres EES dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
than a lifetime of thinking about it nte—# fare dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
thana lifetime of thinking about it nte—# fare de FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
reflect refine repeat antes de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
reflect refine repeat ae ites dae #45: XOCECE Q RAR
reflect refine repeat ne ites de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you know life doesn't improve onset FE waa ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
just because you keep moving forward AG — HBB de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
just because you keep moving forward EAG— HBB ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it improves when you Stop and look back with purpose “nee PRELBw, te Cie) due FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it improves when you Stop and look back with purpose “anges PREABw, te ee) dae F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it improves when you Stop and look back with purpose 4raeontS PREAGH, ca cries dns FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it improves when you Stop and look back with purpose 4raeontS PREAGH, ca cries dae FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
too many people go from one day to the next ASWAM—AHE-R de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
too many people go from one day to the next ASWAM—AHE-A dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one task to the next —MEsE) R—MES dus 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
one task to the next —EsE) R-MES dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
one goal to the next —tke—e dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
without ever asking the Most important MRRAER Sy dwe F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
without ever asking the most important MRRAER BS Ey dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
how did Ido today RAMS EAR? dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
how did Ido today ROAM EAR? dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's where the growth lives amet tenth dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
not just in the doing but in the reviewing inet, MATE AA de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not just in the doing but in the reviewing inte, MATE AA dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not just in the doing but in the reviewing Rinteth, MATE ASA dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
Jim Roan used to say Bis: F Basns dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
a life worth living isa life worth recording ASIN ARERR HLS de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
a life worth living isa life worth recording ASIN BREA FCRHLS ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
alife worth living isa life worth recording ASIN E BREA FCRHLS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and I'lladd this MER. dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
a life worth recording isa life that keeps improving mean tenunasin A dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
a life worth recording isa life that keeps improving mecam tenunasin A des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
a life worth recording isa life that keeps improving mpoam tenunasin A dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now let's break this down PEL BABE DR ds 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
now let's break this down PEL BAHBE DR dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
at the end of your hour TERA BYERS owe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
not the beginning dvs FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not later not tomorrow but at the end of your hour FRR, REBR, MEE I) BT Z5 RAT dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not later not tomorrow but at the end of your hour FEMABHE, REWK, MEE I) BT Z5 RAT de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
not later not tomorrow but at the end of your hour FREE, REAR, MEE — I) BT25 RAT dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
take 5 minutes to reflect #55) Fhe de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
take 5 minutes to reflect 255) Fhe sR dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what did you learn what did you accomplish MEET tA? (TEM T tA? de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
what did you learn what did you accomplish FET tA? mre T +A? dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what did you learn what did you accomplish MFET tA? mre T +A? dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
what did you struggle with once ZU RZ dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
what will you do better tomorrow PRAIA Ht Z BaF de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
what will you do better tomorrow PARRA Ht Z BaF dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not complicated RHR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's just honest dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and most people won't do it KEBMAFERA ML de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and most people won't do it KEBAFERALHL dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
why because it forces them to face their own patterns AAR ARIE eta A OHS dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
why because it forces them to face their own patterns AAR ARIE Hetil A OAS dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
why because it forces them to face their own patterns AAR ARIE tia BOARS dus 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
why because it forces them to face their own patterns AAR ARIE tia A OAS dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it reveals whether they're Moving forward awa CBR T tule Se Bu aE dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it reveals whether they're Moving forward awa HBR T tiles Bet ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
orjust spinning in place ened hery de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but here's the power exe 7S dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but here's the power exe 7] due #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
reflection creates clarity Rat elere dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
reflection creates clarity Rat eneie oT de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
clarity creates improvement FA Mronsaat dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and improvement creates results aan dus F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and improvement creates results aan te dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
now once you've reflected don't stop there EMRE FB RILS de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now once you've reflected don't stop there —SMRRBT FBR dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
now once you've reflected don't stop there —SMRRBT FBR dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
next refine what can be tightened seen T oy dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
next refine what can be tightened se PRCT oy de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
next refine what can be tightened se PRCA ET ey dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
what can be removed what can be added improved upgraded BY LARIBR AT Ze BY LADO Ze PRIA ER dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
what can be removed what can be added improved upgraded BY LARIBR AT Za BY LARD Ze PRIA ER dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what can be removed what can be added improved upgraded BY LARIBR AT Ze BY LARD Ze PRIA ER de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
what can be removed what can be added improved upgraded BY LARIBR AT Za BY LARD Ze PRIA ER dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
simplified de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need to overhaul your life every week MPBES ABM RSME SE des #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you don't need to overhaul your life every week MPBES ADM RSME de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need to overhaul your life every week MPBES ADM REE SE des #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you just need to tweak the process little by little RRB a ate SE de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you just need to tweak the process little by little RRB a— ate SE dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you just need to tweak the process little by little REA ae SE dus FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
because excellence isn't a giant leap Aa RtlAS—T BAW OR dws 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
because excellence isn't a giant leap Aa RtAS—T BAW OR dss 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's a series of Small intelligent corrections sxe—n5i/) AYE BEE IE das 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's a series of Small intelligent corrections see—ao/|\A0 SS BEE IE dss 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's a series of Small intelligent corrections sxee—a5/|\A0 SS BEE IE dws #485: XOCECE Q RAR
overthink of it like EAST de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
airplanes are off course 90 percent of the time @ Tens 9070 BY TE) sae Ae dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
airplanes are off course 90 percent of the time e@ Tena o070H BT TE) sees Ae de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
airplanes are off course 90 percent of the time e@ Tena o070H BT 1) oes A dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
but they constantly adjust sextet 7S ET ad de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
but they constantly adjust sentir 7S ET ad owe $485: XOCECE Q RARE
and guess what EAB? de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
they still land exactly where they' re Supposed to e CAB EMSS de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they still land exactly where they' re Supposed to e CNB EE ASS dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
why because they reflect refine and repeat rT) AA, BAST ERAS S das 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
why because they reflect refine and repeat rT) AA, BAST ESS de $485: XOCECE Q RAR
why because they reflect refine and repeat rT) AA, BAtNRT EAS S ds 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
why because they reflect refine and repeat rT) AA, BACT RASS de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that's your formula sme iM axt dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now every hour you invest in yourself reflect on it r DEER OS HS ioe —hatanes BZ Esl de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
now every hour you invest in yourself reflect on it e DEINE AOS Le Aig —atente BZ fist dwe 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
now every hour you invest in yourself reflect on it e WEES OS 8 ioe —hatanes BZ a de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
refine it repeat it tomorrow just a little better e MHC, ARBBS—B, REV—A. dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
refine it repeat it tomorrow just a little better e MHC, AABBS—iB, REF—A. de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
refine it repeat it tomorrow just a little better e MHC, AABBS—iB, REF—A. dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
do that for a week you'll notice a shift @ RAMA, Meit REIS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
do that for a week you'll notice a shift @ KAW A, metB BBL due 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
do that for a week you'll notice a shift ) RMB, malt RBIS de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
do that fora month ‘ik-TA dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
people will notice AMBER de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
people will notice AMBER dwe 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
do it fora year Ce de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
your life will never be the same one e318 7S FEE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
your life will never be the same one 3818 7 EE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because those who learn from experience grow slow @ ABE MESS Poy A BRC des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because those who learn from experience grow slow @ ABE MESS Poy A BRC dx FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but those who lea rn from evaluated experience e ome MEE ASIP soy A ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but those who lea rn from evaluated experience e Be MEE HAE ISPS soy A de 44H S: XOCECE OQ RARE
but those who lea rm from evaluated experience e OMe MEE HeSIS PS sy A dss #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
they grow fast EATRFRIR de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
they grow strong sense SAL dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they grow wise ‘fh ATT SEAS HEAR de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
so don't just live your life PUB Bw RES dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so don't just live your life PAB BW REE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
examine it shape it BMEBsEe dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
examine it shape it BREBsEe de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
elevate it reflect refine repeat e Rice Rates ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
elevate it reflect refine repeat e Rice RAesS de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
elevate it reflect refine repeat e Rice RaAesS des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how you go from ordinary to exceptional e SRE ME AE Se dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how you go from ordinary to exceptional e SRE IME AE Se dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
dae 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of health a day keeps the doctor away e sx— hatigemit EE xen de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of health a day keeps the doctor away e sr— \atigemit EE stn dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of health a day keeps the doctor away e sr— \atiogemit BE stn de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
let me tell you something that most people forget e IRA HASH A Rian SIS dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
let me tell you something that most people forget e LRA HASRA RINSE dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
your body is not just a vehicle ean inE—t Eh dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
your body is not just a vehicle mean —+ Eh R de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it's the engine of your life eect tis | dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's the engine of your life eect tis | de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and if the engine fails sue 5 | BERR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and if the engine fails 5 | BARR de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't matter how big your dreams are e@ nny aSAHREE dvs #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't matter how big your dreams are e@ tnt SARs SAHRER de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't matter how Clear your goals are e FEN Bina SA dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't matter how Clear your goals are e FSi Bina SA dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't matter how Clear your goals are e FE Bina Sa dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't even matter how much money's in your account e MKP BRS VEBERA de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't even matter how much money's in your account e MKP BRS VEBRRA dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
because when health breaks down everything slows downs RAseenat, BSS ls de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because when health breaks down everything slows downs RAYeeMa, BSS dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
because when health breaks down everything slows downs RAYeeMa, BS Ss de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
because when health breaks down everything slows downs RAYReMR, BSS 1S dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you see the body and the mind are connected ) nee ha BB emee de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you see the body and the mind are connected e@ nee ha BB emee des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't think strai ht when you're tire ) ROR RS dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't think strai ht when you're tire ) RON RES des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't lead when you're weak sneeagay BY {ea ae SS de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't lead when you're weak eneeagay BY a ae S dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you can't build when you're burnt out ry SBRARY, MABE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't build when you're burnt out e@ SBRARY, MARIE ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so what do we do BRATAEAD? de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
we invest one hour a day BISRRA— at dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
inthe most important machine you'll ever e anetE S Snes de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
inthe most important machine you'll ever e enet le S Snes dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
inthe most important machine you'll ever e ainet le S Snes dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now listen I'm not saying you need to be a body builder e he, SRB MS IS mR dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now listen I'm not saying you need to be a body builder e he, RRBWOBERA MEI mA de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
now listen I'm not saying you need to be a body builder e he, RRB ERA -MERIS mA dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm not saying you need to run marathons e@ arene Shits de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm not saying you need to run marathons e@ RrennmEl Shieh dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm not saying you need to run marathons e@ RreiinmEl Shieh de FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
but | am saying you need to move @ RBs SAC dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
but | am saying you need to move @ RBs SAC de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you need to breathe PBB dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
you need to Stretch one eR — FE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you need to Stretch ones tH B— TF dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you need to Sweat because when you honor your health e PRET, BSS BS RAY GER By de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you need to SWeat because when you honor your health e PRET, By Str BS RAY GER Bt dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you elevate your energy oniettT one ES de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you elevate your energy niet ME dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and when your energy goes up Yn Ge Se EABt de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
and when your energy goes up Yn Bee b ABT dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
your results go UP with it nents Remie LF dns #485: XOCECE Q RARE
let me Say that again ILRI dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
let me Say that again ILRI de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
energy is the fuel for achievement e AEB mane des BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
energy is the fuel for achievement @ AES eae de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
want more focus move SEES RSD) dwe 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
want more focus move aeEsw i misay done #485: XOCECE Q RARE
want more drive sweat eEEsnitak dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
want more drive sweat eEEsiitak de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
want more peace sEEswAle dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
breathe deeply RF de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
and the best part it doesn't take all day e gene, chmE—EBR, dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part it doesn't take all day e gene, chmE—EBR., de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part it doesn't take all day e gene, chmE—EBR., dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
one focused hour E— de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's it walk in the morning stretch your body e RE, PLB, RS dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's it walk in the morning stretch your body e RE, PLES, RNS dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's it walk in the morning stretch your body e RAR, PLR, RMS dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
do some yoga lift some weights e Pest Tip de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
do some yoga lift some weights e ee FAT (Masa dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
or simply Step outside and get the sun on your face e meneehx, uBbAstmemoe et de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
or simply Step outside and get the sun on your face e menecux, ultimo ds 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
or simply Step outside and get the sun on your face e menecux, ultimo de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and the air in your lungs xem Bass dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the air in your lungs xem Bass de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's a Jim Roan ane: Fe dvs 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
Care of your body rami 1h dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's the only place you have to live @ xem A de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's the only place you have to live @ meee aE dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
now let me give you a warning meine de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
now let me give you a warning merieean—T SS dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
neglect is quiet at first an—riee RaM de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
neglect is quiet at first an Fie RiM dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
afew skipped workouts a few too many processed meals @ rime, MLR dns #485: XOCECE Q RARE
afew skipped workouts a few too many processed meals e ene, DIT R dae 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
afew skipped workouts a few too many processed meals e ene, DITA de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
a few extra hours sitting in that chair and suddenly @ ERBKGF LSB )et dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
afew extra hours sitting in that chair and suddenly @ ERBKGF LSB) et de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
afew extra hours sitting in that chair and suddenly @ ERBKBF LES et dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
afew extra hours sitting in that chair and suddenly @ ERBKBF LES et de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the body starts breaking down e@ Shane ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the body starts breaking down e@ Siren de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
not all at once but slowly silently ® ARTS, mE SH ABH dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
not all at once but slowly silently e ARTS, mE BSH RAH de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
not all at once but slowly silently e ARTS, mE SH RAH dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
until one day the price shows up in the doctor's Bill e@ xan ee de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
until one day the price shows up in the doctor's Bill ry ie Sh Sa des #485: XOCECE Q RARE
until one day the price shows up in the doctor's Bill ry SiS Sa de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
in the energy crash TREMP dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
in the energy crash TREMP de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
inthe missed opportunity eis konae dws #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you weren't Strong enough to grab e mre MARZ de FBS: XOCECE OQ RHR
you weren't Strong enough to grab e ree AL MRE dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
discipline weighs ounces aren de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
discipline weighs ounces Parad dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
regret weighs tons cabal de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so take the hour rane dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so take the hour rate de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
protect the hour dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
use it to build your strength not just your Skills e Ree, mremetn aot BE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
use it to build your strength not just your Skills e meee 71S, mremem ete BE dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
use it to build your strength not just your Skills e Ree, mremetn aot BE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because you can't give your best patn 7 BES A Duh dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
because you can't give your best patn 7 BES A ruth de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're running on empty snes 35 9018, dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't lead others if you can't even lift yourself e MRNA MARR, tat ABEM Sal de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
you can't lead others if you can't even lift yourself e MRNA MARR, ta ABEM Sal dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you can't lead others if you can't even lift yourself e RIMES BAAR, Mat AE SRK dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and you can't live your purpose ACE comers Eth ds $485: XOCECE Q RARE
and you can't live your purpose Ak somes Eth de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're constantly managing pain e RBS HR dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
if you're constantly managing pain e RBS HA de 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
so Starting today PRAMS RAS dws FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
treat your health like your future depends onit e XTRA FE Rertem RTE tH de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
treat your health like your future depends onit e XTRA FE Rare RRT E —# dvs #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
treat your health like your future depends onit e XTRA FE ReremeRRTE tH de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because it does tf enue dae #485: XOCECE Q RAR
one hour a day to walk SRST de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour a day to walk SRST dws 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
to stretch to fuel tH CARS} owe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
to stretch to fuel 18 CARS} dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
to rest to keep the doctor away and success close by e ea, Bas, imoneeR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
to rest to keep the doctor away and success close by e ea, iBAas, imonreeR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
to rest to keep the doctor away and success close by e ea, LBAas, ibmonreeR de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
to rest to keep the doctor away and success close by e ea, LBAas, imoneeR dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
build a fortune in the quiet hour @ BATH dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
build a fortune in the quiet hour e@ BATH de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
let me tell you something important e iLRsainHKBS SH S85 dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
let me tell you something important e Les HKBEH SS de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
profits are better than wages ALAS dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
profits are better than wages ALAS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
wages make you a living but profits e LHestiteFlig dws #45: XOCECE Q RAR
wages make you a living but profits e LHestiteFlid de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
wages make you a living but profits e LHestiteFlig dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they make you a fortune Hei AZ NA de #45: XOCECE Q RAR
and to build profits you don't need 10 hours a day e AT ANISFUT, mamesxlOPy Bt des FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and to build profits you don't need 10 hours a day e AT ANIA, ameexlOPy at de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and to build profits you don't need 10 hours a day e aT ASF, mareeex1lOhy Bt dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and to build profits you don't need 10 hours a day e AT ANIA, mameexlOP at de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need ateam mares lB, dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't even need permission @ reeRRE TT A] de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you need one hour one quiet hour e@ onmee— | ES — + 2 af at dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you need one hour one quiet hour ry onpe— | VES — + 2 af et de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you need one hour one quiet hour ry onmpe— | VES — + 2 aa at dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
now most people get home from work and they Shut down @ MEASBATHEREBS RK IAG de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
now most people get home from work and they shut down @ MEASBA THEREMS RA! IAG dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
now most people get home from work and they Shut down @ MEASBATHEREMSR! IAG dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they say I've done enough eT RR IE OS ZT owe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so they sit scroll watch and wonder why nothing changes @ PROMISE ODER, META HARE. de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
so they sit scroll watch and wonder why nothing changes @ PROMISE ODER LE, AMBIT A HAM. dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so they sit scroll watch and wonder why nothing changes e@ PROMISE ODER, AME TA HARE. de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so they sit scroll watch and wonder why nothing changes e@ PROMISE ODER, AMEE HAM. des FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
so they sit scroll watch and wonder why nothing changes e@ PROMISE ODER, AME TA HAM. de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
but that ree hour right before right after dinner e men MER aw Barb st dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but pecquict hour right before right after dinner e soeemarl {Faas SBS AT IE de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
but pequict hour right before right after dinner e soemarle {Faas Sa AT IE dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's your chance wen NLS de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's your Space to build something that's YOUrS r REM SA RBERF MOR dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's your Space to build something that's YOUrs r REM SA RBERF MOR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's your Space to build something that's YOUrS r REM SA RBERF MHRA dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not for your OSS not for your paycheck e FRAT He, REA ST (AVR de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
not for your bOSS not for your paycheck @ RENT Hei, REA ST (AV RRAK des #485: XOCECE Q RAR
not for your OSS not for your paycheck @ FRAT Mei, BEAT AV RRAK de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but for your future THEA T RAR dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
in that hour you can Start your side business @ x Nata FPG RAY Be de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
in that hour you can Start your side business e@ x hata FP GS RAY Be dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you can learn anew skill RATS — ATER BE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can learn anew skill ARATE SITTER BE dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you can Write you can plan you can Sell you can build e PATAS TE, MALT L, MATH, tr ALBIS de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you can write you can plan you can Sell you can build e PRATAS TE, MATL, MATH, te ALBIS dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can write you can plan you can Sell you can build e PRATAS TE, MATL, MATH, te ALBIS de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need a fancy office ARERR EA TDA dwe 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need a fancy office ARBRE TD de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you don't need a perfect setup MPBE—TREVE dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't need a perfect setup MPBE—TRENE de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
you just need a little hunger REE aa dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and one hour that you don't give to the world e Bane a AR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and one hour that you don't give to the world e Bain BER dwe $485: XOCECE Q RAR
and one hour that you don't give to the world e Bain BER de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
now let me be honest mee IGRI, dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the results won't come ina day but that's Not the goal © genee—KAue, exteB To dns #45: XOCECE Q RAR
the results won't come ina day but that's Not the goal © genee—KAue, extheB To dwe #45: XOCECE Q RAR
the results won't come ina day but that's Not the goal e genee—KAue, extheB To done BS: XOCECE Q RAR
the goalis momentum Binesn dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
one houra day five hours a week e RT I-A Bet de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
one houra day five hours a week e RT) AB dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
one houra day five hours a week e@ RT) AB de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
260 hours a year —#260.)et dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's not small BATA de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's not small BATA dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
that's massive xeBA de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's a product launched that 'sa brand started e@ ome a —+ mahFeo a dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
that's a product launched that 'sa brand started e@ a TT —+ hPa ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's a future created sate fiw dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's a future created sate iene de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
but only if you treat the hour like treasure @ deaiiee oe y [e] ne Se HL dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but only if you treat the hour like treasure @ deaiiee oe Ay [B] see Se HL de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
not as time to waste but time to build @ FERMI, MBZIZTIG) dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
not as time to waste but time to build @ FERMI, MBZIZT a) dns #485: XOCECE Q RAR
not as time to waste but time to build @ FERMI, MBZIZTG) de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you don't build wealth with wishes r) TRAE de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you build it with work ir (PRE dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you build it with work nL (PRE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
quiet focused consistent work when no one's watching r ) eeAaMRT aS LE dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
quiet focused consistent work when no one's watching @ ee ant ae LE de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
quiet focused consistent work when no one's watching @ ee atin aS LE dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
quiet focused consistent work when no one's watching @ ee atin ae LE de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and here's the best xemotiy dwe #43: XOCECE Q RARE
if you do that long enough soem eH AE 3 TC BY BY] de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
if you do that long enough soem e TE 3 TAY BY] dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
one day you'll look up and realize something e RA—Ansem de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one day you'll look up and realize something e RA—Aneem dwe $483: XOCECE Q RARE
that little hour built your confidence e@ BB BHI T HAV de BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
that little hour built your confidence e@ BB BHI T HAV ads des BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that little hour built your confidence e@ BB BHI T HAV sds de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
built your income ZW eo des 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
built your independence seven 37 LE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and it started when you made one simple decision e ene inky —-MB) BRE, dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
and it started when you made one simple decision e ene iy —M EB RE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and it started when you made one simple decision e ene inky —MB) BRE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
to stop WaSting the quiet hour Bik ibe Be SCART IA] de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
to stop WaSting the quiet hour Bib Tbe Be SCHOO AT IA] dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
and start using it to build your fortune @ HAMAERTRR IHS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and start using it to build your fortune @ HAMACRAR IHS dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
relationships built one hour at atime @ RB UHRA dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
relationships built one hour at atime @ RBH RA de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
relationships built one hour at atime @ RB UHRA dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
now let's talk about something e PLTEIL BATRA de 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
most success books leave out @ ASB AMI LT dwe BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
most success books leave out @ ASBMB ST de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
relationships KR dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
because what good is a fortune aA BB tt Zs RE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because what good is a fortune aH BB tt Zs dwe F4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
what good is a Strong body BRITA S heat sre de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what good is a Strong body BRITA SS heat sre dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
asharp mind a big bank account @ Liviesst, (RTGS de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
asharp mind a big bank account e Liviesst, (RTF Rs dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
if you don't have people to share it with @ RINEHART LS de FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
if you don't have people to share it with e@ MRI BA ALIS dws FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
success without connectionisempty @ RARER SHN de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
success without connectionisempty @ RABE RES owe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
success without connectionisempty @ RABE RSS de 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't build a good life ermearesrseerey EG dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
just by building businesses or habits @ de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
just by building businesses or habits @ de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
just by building businesses or habits @ dss 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you build a good life by building people e ones A sere seers EIS dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
you build a good life by building people e reste eA sre seerey EG de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and that takes time ie Zential., dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and that takes time ie 2eatial, de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
that takes care ame/|vty dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
that takes presence Was Sete de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
but here's the good news YF dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
but here's the good news YF de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
just like you grow wealth with one quiet hour e mame an eae I Se ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
just like you grow wealth with one quiet hour e mame Sa eae Se de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you grow relationships the same way e@ AmeAEEHY Fy TL ALR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
you grow relationships the same way e@ REL EUEHFT TL BRA de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
you grow relationships the same way @ REL EUEOFT TL BRA dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour atatime RT NT de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour atatime RT NT dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of real conversation one hour of listening 6 NAUSEA ET BOOT de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of real conversation one hour of listening 6 — a AISLE) BT BY HO dss #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of real conversation one hour of listening 6 NUR TIE— NT BOOT de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
not just hearing FRM dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
not just hearing de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of putting the phone down e@ Bereag— | ET de #5: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of putting the phone down e@ Bereag— ET de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and looking someone in the eyes e eax Anika dvs BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and looking someone in the eyes e eax Anika de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you see people don't. remember what you Said e BMTRIC HF emtat tt dwe F4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you see people don't. remember what you Said e BMIRIC HF emtat tt de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they remember how you made them feel e@ eT ee HATH dwe BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
they remember how you made them feel e@ eed ine tec de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and they feel it when you give them time @ Senate ATAL SEY, HTS ete SAY ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and they feel it when you give them time @ Sema ATAT SET, HTS be SAY de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and they feel it when you give them time @ Senate TAL iS eY, HTS ete SIAy ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now I'm not asking for 10 hours a week e@ MER EER Lio hat de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now I'm not asking for 10 hours a week @ MERE aL Fo hat dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm not asking you to become a therapist e areena SRE de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
I'm not asking you to become a therapist e areena SER E dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
all I'm saying is RAH S de 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
all I'm saying is RAKE dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
give someone in your life sane BERANE A de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
your full attention for just one hour ry eRe de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
your full attention for just one hour e@ 2eRE— de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
your Spouse your child ene Bic fat AF dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
your Spouse your child neve tn AF de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
your parent your mentor your friend ry PRAISO RBS S UBB AB AZ dvs #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
your parent your mentor your friend ry PRAISO RBS S UBB AB AZ dus #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
your parent your mentor your friend ry PRAISO RBS SUB BY AB AZ dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and don't just Sit in the same room @ FRERese tee de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and don't just Sit in the Same room @ ER2se tee ds 4B S: XOCECE OQ RARE
be there ask questions share stories e ensliaoss de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
be there ask questions share stories e ans iwaosts ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
be there ask questions share stories e ans aosts de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
laugh alittle or just sit together and be quiet e R—-RKysnese LRH dwe 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
laugh alittle or just sit together and be quiet e R—-Rsnese LRH de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
laugh alittle or just sit together and be quiet e R—-Rysnese LRH dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because presence is powerful BAREE RAM de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
because presence is powerful BAREE RAM dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
let me tell you what happens when you do this @ LESTE SS ee de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
let me tell you what happens when you do this e SERS eee SS ee dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
trust starts to grow walls begin {BE ittamc, sar iacn de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
trust starts to grow walls begin to fall e@ {BE Etamic, saree dss 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
trust starts to grow walls begin to fall e@ {BE Etamic, saree de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
love multiplies and connection deepens e za, Ame ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
love multiplies and connection deepens e za, Ame de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
love multiplies and connection deepens e za, Ame ds 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
it doesn't take a fancy dinner or a big trip e CARRE we BHM Be — Rie aR de BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it doesn't take a fancy dinner or a big trip e CARE we BHR Be— Rise Re dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't take a fancy dinner or a big trip e CARE we BHM Be— Rie ies de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it takes one hour of your heart with no distractions @ BE) AT eoeas dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it takes one hour of your heart with no distractions e@ BER) Ay eoees dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it takes one hour of your heart with no distractions e@ BEM) MT eoees dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and I'll Say this RAR de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
and I'll Say this RAR dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
the people who know how to build great relationships @ Se TIBI AFR FAA de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
the people who know how to build great relationships @™ SISO TIT AFR FAA dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they always Win in the long run IGERE, HIRE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they always Win in the long run MERE, HIRE dws FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because in the storms Of life and they will come e@ mnt H MR, ties de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because in the storms Of life and they will come e@ mnt AMER, ties dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
because in the storms Of life and they will come e@ mane R, ties de #483: XOCECE Q RARE
money won't hold your hand Raw eHF dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
money won't hold your hand Raw eHF de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
SUCCESS won't hug you but relationships will e MIpreimien, GAMERS en de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
SUCCESS won't hug you but relationships will e Mra, CARS de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
SUCCESS won't hug you but relationships will e Mra, CARS ds 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
so schedule that hour PROACHES Bt de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
make it intentional BBAZ dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
because if you don't invest in people e BARR RAF A de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
because if you don't invest in people e BAMA RAF A dvs 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll wake up one day surrounded by things e a Kieren Bem de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
you'll wake up one day surrounded by things e a—Kiexswenk Bem dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
you'll wake up one day surrounded by things e a—Aiexswenk Bem de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
but feeling completely alone ees S MIR dwe #483: XOCECE Q RAR
but feeling completely alone eenseS MIR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and here's the dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
arich life is measured in memories not just milestonesy FROLEEMIZAOEM, MALLE Bee de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
arich life is measured in memories not just milestonesy FROLEEMIZAOEM, MALLE Bee dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
arich life is measured in memories not just milestonesy SRNESRMCCAOEM, MALE Bee dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
arich life is measured in memories not just milestonesy SRMESRMCICROEM, MALE Bee dwe 4B S: XOCECE Q RAR
and Memories are made in moments @ idiZemiah? Bes de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and Memories are made in moments e@ idlZemiah? Bes ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
moments like this moments that begin with just one hour @ sgaxHeHoEzd M+] VES Re de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
moments like this moments that begin with just one hour @ sgoxHeHNEzd M+] VES Re dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
moments like this moments that begin with just one hour @ sgaxHeHNEd Mt) VES Re de 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
so the next time you think about SUCCeSS remember this PRIA PR OMAR RROD ERIC (EI — sR des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
so the next time you think about SUCCeSS remember this, FRA RR OMAR ERODE IC (EIS — sR de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
so the next time you think about SUCCeSS remember this, FRUL PROM ER ODI (EIS — sR des 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
so the next time you think about SUCCeSS remember this, FRU RR AMAR ERODE IC (EIS — sR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
don't just build your future FER nae dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
build your people and do it one hour ata time ry SFR AL, —xte—taet de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
build your people and do it one hour ata time e@ SFR AL, —xth—tat dvs #485: XOCECE Q RARE
build your people and do it one hour ata time e@ SFR AL, —xth—tat de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
dae #485: XOCECE Q RARE
stack your hours sean ensg BY [5] de F4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
stack your hours seein BY 18) dws FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
stack your future SEM ong de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you've heard it before PreceOat dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
success is built one step ata time e mop — 25 —“S i) El ert sen de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
success is built one step ata time r ) mepe— 25 —“S Ha) Ee rte sen dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
success is built one step ata time @ mepe— 25 —“S ha Ee rte sen de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
well I'll say it a little differently son, EIR Stsk. dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
well l'll say it a little differently son, eet Stsk. de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
SUCCESS is built One hour ata time r ) PI — IRB RAY dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
SUCCESS is built One hourata time  ) PRIDE VIR TRAY de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of discipline BT MER dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of learning one hour of building @ I Nate de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of learning one hour of building @ I Nate dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of learning one hour of building S NI Nate de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of investing in your mind your body e eM MAT een aaa dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour of investing in your mind your body e ev VAS ee aaa E de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of investing in your mind your body e ew NAS een aaa des FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
your future now here's the problem e eae seul de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
your future now here's the problem e cae eM dss FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
most people underestimate what one hour a day can dom AKBRMMAT —R— REIT dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
most people underestimate what one hour a day can dom ABRMMAT —R— BRET A de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
most people underestimate what one hour a day can dom ABRMMAT —R— BRET A dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they say it's just an hour HoT RB— Pat de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
they say it's just an hour HHT RB at dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
what difference does it make xattak all de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what difference does it make xattakall dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
let me Show you the math ibe TN RS de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour a day that's seven hours a week e@ RK ste C yet ds #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
one hour a day that's seven hours a week e@ RK she C yet de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour a day that's seven hours a week e@ RK shea yet ds FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
that's over 300 hours a year —# #8300109 de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's over 300 hours a year —# #8 300n09 des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's more than Seven full time work weeks ry gu7anSin Le de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that's more than Seven full time work weeks e@ au7mn2A Le dae 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now ask yourself REARS de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
das #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you Sick of reading nlR ET IR de #45: XOCECE AY Q RABE
well speechify makes it easy to learn on the fly e well speechify fH BN At 5) B45 oe ° dvs Speechify — Text t... #8: xocECE AY ay Install Q Reta
well speechify makes it easy to learn on the fly e well speechify{# BUAY 4 >) 45 rE de Speechify — Text t... #8: xocECE AY ty, Install Q Rta
well speechify makes it easy to learn on the fly e well speechify(# BNAY 34 >) 3545 se dwe Speechify — Text t... aiabinean im) pmeppcecnity = lex Install Q seta
| have to doa lot of reading for my job e ATRHLURRBRRS B Skip >I dss Speechify — Text t... #8: xocECE AY ay, Install Q Rta
| have to do a lot of reading for my job e AT ROI ERAE SB dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
what could you do with seven full time weeks @ CT SER A erecta? de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
what could you do with seven full time weeks e@ CS SER A treet a? dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
focused only on growth Rettig de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
focused only on growth avitrigik due #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you could write a book learn a high value skill e RATS As, ean EBX Be de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you could write a book learn a high value skill e PRET As, ean MMEBIIR aE dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you could write a book learn a high value skill e PRET As, ean MMEBIIR aE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
build a business change your health e@ bu Ndesnorg dns BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
build a business change your health e@ puNdescorg de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
master your mindset or even rebuild your life e SRR DAaseennes des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
master your mind set or even rebuild your life e Siem wezs SERVES de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
master your mind set or even rebuild your life e Sieimhiwezs SERVES dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but you don't doitina rush eR wth de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
you do it by Stacking the hours one on tOp of another @ Pie ae eee ee dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you do it by Stacking the hours one on tOp of another @ Pia ies ee eee dus FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you do it by Stacking the hours one on tOp of another @ vi a ee meee! dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you do it by Stacking the hours one on tOp of another @ vi ae ee eee! de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
each one building on the last brick by brick e st seme—e—-EHHiZis dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
each one building on the last brick by brick e st Seme—e-BHhi2i8 de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
each one building on the last brick by brick e st Seme—e-EHhi2iS dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
quiet steady strong Riherwt de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
quiet steady strong Rierwt dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how a future is built ARMBRHIS IER de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
that's how a future is built ARMBRYIE IER des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
not in a burst of energy but in consistent effort e@ FREER, —— de #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
not in a burst of energy but in consistent effort e@ FREER, Lipa Ee ds 44BS: XOCECE Q RARE
_ now here's the small disciplines don't stay smalls REFERS RHE. de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
_ now here's the small disciplines don't stay smalls REFRESH. dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RAR
_ now here's the small disciplines don't stay smalls REFRESH. dus #485: XOCECE Q RARE
_ now here's the small disciplines don't stay smalls RENFNRS RH. dove FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
they expand they multiply they shape who you become e em sk, AGT, meme. de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
they expand they multiply they shape who you become e ey sk, AGT, weave. ds 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they expand they multiply they shape who you become e ey sk, ATT, wena ve. de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they expand they multiply they shape who you become e ey ak, AGT, meme. ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
every time you ShOW Up for that hour e@ serine PTE de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
every time you Show Up for that hour e@ serntem PHT LE dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you're Casting a vote for your future e iene MARIS de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
you're Casting a vote for your future e Irene oR dvs FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you're saying I'm not wasting my life e MERA A RAE de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you're saying I'm not wasting my life e MERBRA RAE dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm not waiting on luck RABESEAD de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm building something that matt Hews —ts ers @ Ew TRG dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
I'm building something that matters r Res Keen RG ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and that decision made daily creates momentum e SRM OLET DTI des 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
and that decision made daily creates momentum e SRM OST DT de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and that decision made daily creates momentum e SRAM OST DT de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it creates confidence eansy fab de BS: XOCECE Q RAR
it creates confidence eansy fab dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
it creates results because when you add up the hours e ea ER, wy veniaationns de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it creates results because when you add up the hours e ea ER, wy venient dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it creates results because when you add up the hours e ea ER, wy veniaationnes dus 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you add up the progress endo DEC HE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and when you add up the progress e pam DEC SR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and when you add up the progress e spans DEC SR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you start changing your identity e onrronerse one 1} de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you start changing your identity e onrronerse ene 1} dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you go from someone who waits to someone who builds ry onh—MESBY A some A de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you go from someone who waits to someone who builds e@ on—MESHY A some A, dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RAR
you go from someone who waits to someone who builds e@ in — MESA A seme A, dus #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
now listen there will be days you miss It r) Whe, RARE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
now listen there will be days you miss It @ he, RARE de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
that's okay you're human BRAMBARK dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
that's okay you're human RRAMBAR de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but don't let a missed hour turn intoa missed week ry SFR yeas des #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
but don't leta missed hour turn intoa missed week ry PFRiLBIH— ss ees — A de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
but don't let a missed hour turn intoa missed week @ PFRiLBMH— gS essa ds #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
ora missed year eset 7 — FE de F4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
always come back BEER dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
get back to Stacking ElBiem de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
because time is passing either way e@ mare sHebt el aRe mish dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
because time is passing either way @ mare sHeby el aBe mish de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
and one day the question won' t did you dream big it'll e BRK, KNABRAILBMRA, C e & dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and one day the question won' t did you dream big it'll e aR, SMABRAILMBMRA, C Ms & de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and one day the question won' t did you dream big it't e aR, SMABRAILB MRA, C Ms & ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and one day the question won' t did you dream big it'll e aR, SMABRAILMBMTA, C Ms & de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
did you use your hours wisely one BAS Hh cera 7 mes BY lal? ds #485: XOCECE Q RARE
did you use your hours wisely one BAS Hh cera 7 mes BY lal? de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so Stack them protect them muifecnteiPen de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
so Stack them protect them muiufeentiPen de #483: XOCECE Q RARE
and one day you'll look up a—Rmsigrs dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and one day you'll look up a—Rmsigrse de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and realize you didn't just change your habits e morse FSR de HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
and realize you didn't just change your habits e mona SSR de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
you changed your life enegae 7 oboe 3G dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you changed your life enegae Tenby E75 de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
when One hour turns into a new you @ SMS R—TS BIEN dwe 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
when One hour turns into a new you @ S—MSR—TS MIN dus #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
when One hour turns into a new you e S—MSR—TS MAIN ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you started west 1 hour one hour of learning ) FER ET Liat yat de 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
you started EUS 1 hour one hour of learning ) FRET Liat yay dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you started EHUSE 1 hour one hour of learning ) FRET Liat yay de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of building one hour of reflecting e TBA) BTR dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of building one hour of reflecting e NBER — NT RB de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of building one hour of reflecting e TBA) ETB BE due FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
one hour of building one hour of reflecting e TBA) ETHIE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
One hour for your health one hour for your future ) ANT A ARBITER 1) BT IRAE doses FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
One hour for your health one hour for your future ) ANT AURIS I BT AI RARE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
One hour for your health one hour for your future ) AN BT AURIS I BT IRAE dvs #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
at first it felt small FBR Ry de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
almost invisible nse dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
almost invisible nsBRR de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
like nothing was happening but day by day e wath ata. g-AR— dws 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
like nothing was happening but day by day e netoe a. @—Fr— de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
hour by hour something was happening e BS ast 5 eR dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
hour by hour something was happening e BY — paste ge de 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
hour by hour something was happening e AY — paste ge dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you were becoming someone new @ nett ATA A, de $45: XOCECE Q RAR
not overnight not by accident but by decision e FEZ, FER, THRE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
not overnight not by accident but by decision e FE-RZ, FEGR, THRE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
not overnight not by accident but by decision e FE-RZA, FEER, MORE ds FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's a truth you can count on @ Bata AA Ex TBR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because here's a truth you can count on @ BAAR XT BS des 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't change your life in one leap e PRA A] BE— FF REE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you don't change your life in one leap e RAB BE— FFE EE dss FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you Change your life one consistent hour ata time @ tra) — Be EL SE PRAY AE FE de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you Change your life one consistent hour ata time @ tra) — Be PL SE PRAY AE FE due #45: XOCECE Q RAR
you Change your life one consistent hour ata time @ tra) — ee LSS PRAY AE FE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you Change your life one consistent hour ata time e@ tra) —/) Be LSE PRAY AE FE dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the hour you Showed up when it wasn't easy e repeat A A de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the hour you Showed up when it wasn't easy e rene Ft ARB A dwe $485: XOCECE Q RARE
the hour you chose growth over comfort @ Meeermneenan sy Zl) de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the hour you chose growth over comfort ry Meeebmneenen sy ZI) ds 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
the hour you practiced instead of postponed e tree mR HE IR osetia de BS: XOCECE Q RARE
the hour you practiced instead of postponed e tree mA HE IR peti dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
the hour you practiced instead of postponed e tree Sma HE IR oes dus #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
the hour you listened loved endo VAT TE dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
the hour you listened loved endemonVAT TE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
focused Sch dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
created and those hours they did something powerful e AUST RALATIAL, hd BRAY B de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
created and those hours they did something powerful e ANS TATA, dT T TRARY B dwe BS: XOCECE Q RARE
created and those hours they did something powerful e AUST RLATIA, ed TRARY B de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
created and those hours they did something powerful e AUST RLATIA, ed T HER ABY B dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
they rewired your mind HH REET tnt) AR de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
they reshaped your habits seed TeET dns >) 1 dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they reshaped your habits eet T dns >) 1 de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
they rebuilt your confidence one hour atatime @ #84] — at ERB (El dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
they rebuilt your confidence one hour ata time @ #84] — at ERA (El de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
they rebuilt your confidence one hour ata time @ #41 net — et ERA (El dss #485: XOCECE Q RARE
you started to believe in yourself again e metits BOT de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
you started to believe in yourself again e mets Bor dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
you began to trust your word mnareeteS (RAVIE T de 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
you proved to yourself tr EAA dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
you proved to yourself tre EB EBA de #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
that discipline isn't just a word ReTRE— NA dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
that discipline isn't just a word Ree NA de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's a lifestyle xe Meeast dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and the best part you didn't need to change everything e RENE RS Ly de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part you didn't need to change everything e RRR NS ey dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and the best part you didn't need to change everything e REE NGS Ly de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you just peste to change one thing e ames — (Ps dwe #45: XOCECE Q RARE
you just gece to change one thing e nme ess de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
how you US@ your time nga) FA nes BST] dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
that was the turning point merci ma de $485: XOCECE OQ RARE
that was the turning point wmeteit ma dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
because if you can control one hour @ mae MnBe ds tall —PS as dss FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because if you can control one hour e@ mae MnBeds tall —P at dss #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
you can eventually control your nee eay ES Hill (RAY —F de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you can eventually control your day e enemy EE Hill RAY —F dwe #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and if you can control your day sos enacts til (RAEY—A de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you can Shape your future rey 2B IS rt ae dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
you can Shape your future ore BBS rt ae de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
so here's what | want you to remember ry PROABRAB LL ARIE dwe #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
so here's what | want you to remember @ PROABRABLL ARIE de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
success is not luck moe dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
it's not mystery it's not magic BREW, treet de #45: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not mystery it's not magic BREW, creek dwe #483: XOCECE Q RARE
it's not mystery it's not magic BRE, trek de #483: XOCECE Q RARE
it's discipline applied daily @ xesxmmnZe ze dwe 44H S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's discipline applied daily @ xesxmmnZo ze de 44H S: XOCECE OQ RARE
and that discipline wamren ze dwe FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it doesn't take everything you' ve got @ CFREIMAAN—Y) de #4BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
it doesn't take everything you' ve got @ CARE IMA —H) dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it just takes one hour every day without feel e SRABE—M RAR de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it just takes one hour every day without feel e SRABE—MN RAR dwe #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
it just takes one hour every day without feel e SRABE—MN RAR de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
without excuses eefaO dws FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
and one day you'll look inthe mirror @ a— Rina F de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
and One day you'll look in the mirror e a— Rial F dae #485: XOCECE Q RAR
and realize you didn't just change your schedule e sonsimaneae 7 i ARH de #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and realize you didn't just change your Schedule e sonsimanneae 7 i ARH due #4BS: XOCECE Q RARE
and realize you didn't just change your Schedule e sunsimaneae 7 on ASHE de 4B S: XOCECE Q RARE
you changed your identity onexse Ty Et  dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
you changed your identity enexse Ty Et  de #HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
you became the kind of person who shows up e onsen 7 ABA LA ELAS A, des 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
you became the kind of person who Shows up e enaent 7 ABA LA ELAS A, de #485: XOCECE Q RAR
who follows through who lives intentionally e HS RERRES dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
who follows through who lives intentionally e HS RERRES de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
who walks in purpose who builds with wisdom ry aAinma, eB enr dwe HBS: XOCECE Q RARE
who walks in purpose who builds with wisdom e@ aAinm,, senna de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
who walks in purpose who builds with wisdom ry aA, a RnAr dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that is the NEW you all from one hour ry sae—/) BT Maren de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
and that is the NEW you all from one hour @ sae—/) BT Waren dwe #485: XOCECE Q RARE
and that is the NEW you all from one hour @ sae—/) BY Waren de 4S: XOCECE Q RARE
so keep it up pre 23e08 due 4S: XOCECE Q RAR
stay consistent RIM de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
protect the hour dwe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
respect the process de FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
respect the process dwe #485: XOCECE OQ RARE
because it's not just how you spend your time e RAMEE fray asia) de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
because it's NOt just how you spend your time e RAM RMS prey asia) dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
it's how you Shape your life maBensnmpeasestinty AE de FBS: XOCECE Q RARE
it's how you Shape your life mB enon mpeasestinty AE dwe 44BS: XOCECE OQ RARE
de 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
start today not tomorrow SRA MREAR dwe FBS: XOCECE OQ RARE
start today not tomorrow SRA MRE AR de 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
now you've heard it all PLEAS T owe 48S: XOCECE OQ RARE
the habits the hour the truth SREY eae de 48S: XOCECE Q RAR
the habits the hour the truth SREY eae dwe 48S: XOCECE Q RARE
the habits the hour the truth SREY eae de #485: XOCECE Q RARE
so what's next I'l tell WAGE PRBS SMTA due Ae CE ie
so what's next I'l tell BASF RBS SIA de we CE iB
start today not tomorrow SRIWGR BAR dss ee CE iB
start today not tomorrow SRA BAR de ae CE iB
because tomorrow isa promise today is a decision AAWRE-NVAIG, SRE-VRIE dwe #48 SeMOCECE BB
because tomorrow isa promise today is a decision AARRE—-NVAIE, SRE-VRIE de #48: MOCECE QeARE
because tomorrow isa promise today is a decision AAWRE-NVAIE, SRE-VRIE dwe #4: XOCECE Q RARE
don't Wait for motivation aESaT de HES; XOCECE QAARE
don't Wait for motivation aESaT dwe $$, XOCECE ORR
don't wait for the right mood sEsaanb is de 48S, KOCECE QRtKis
don't wait for the New Year or Monday FBS MERE dwe #48 S:XOCECE QetRiE
don't wait for the New Year or Monday FBS MERE de 48S, KOCECE Q RARE
or some perfect moment that never shows up Hee Maaraumnee iy Zl due HS, XOCECE Q RARE
or some perfect moment that never shows up RSE acer snmyeeAT Zl) de 48S,XOCECE Q RARE
or some perfect moment that never shows up RHR aaarsnmeyeeAT Hl) dwe 99S,XOCECE QRtKis
just start pick one hour Remiaiae—1/) VEY de #48: XOCECE QRtKis
just start pick one hour Reriame—1/) BY dwe 49S, XOCECE QRtKis
claim it aa de #48; XOCECE BB
schedule it protect it like your future depends onit RHCRPE, wemorerre Ht ds #48: KOCECE QRtKis
schedule it protect it like your future depends onit RHR EC, wemmreWAFE —# de 4S; KOCECE QRtKis
schedule it protect it like your future depends onit RHR CE, wemmoreWAFE tH des 48S, XKOCECE Q RtRis
because it does mat ont de 44S; KOCECE Q RARE
you don't have to be great ABER SRG de #485; XOCECE QAARE
you don't have to have all the answers MARRS NSE de 4S; KOCECE Q RARE
you don't have to have all the answers MARLEE ds 48S, XOCECE Q RARE
you just have to be willing dns #485; XOCECE QAARE
you just have to be willing de #45; XOCECE QAARE
willing to Show up meils de #485; XOCECE QAARE
remember this idtts—a dwe #48; MOCECE BB
change doesn't happen when you now what to do went Ant, MEARS de 48S; KOCECE Q RARE
change doesn't happen when you now what to do went Aat, MEARS RE dwe 48S; KOCECE Q RARE
change happens when you do what you know a aa KERMA de #485; XOCECE QRARE
change happens when you do what you know aaa MERER due 41S; XOCECE QetKia
you've got the Map now one Hy de #485; XOCECE QutKie
you've got the Map now once ST dwe #485; XOCECE QutKie
you've got the Steps you've got the power nt, cans de #45; XOCECE QAARE
you've got the Steps you've got the power nS, cans dws #485; XOCECE QAARE
so don't walk away from this video PRE Fea de #18S:XOCECE Q eatzs
so don't walk away from this video PURE ea ds HHS; XOCECE QAARE
just feeling inspired ReneZZAR de #45; XOCECE ABE
walk away activated #7 BOE due He ECE —_
walk away activated #7 BCE de Hes: ECE BB
decide right now BRE des Hes ECE —
today what hour will you take back what will you build SRMAWEMTARE, MABIETA? de 48S; XOCECE Q RARE
today what hour will you take back what will you build SAMAWEMARE], MABIEA? dws 48S; XOCECE Q RARE
today what hour will you take back what will you build SAMAWEMAIE, MABIEA? de 48S; XOCECE Q RARE
who will you become MERA dwe 48S; XOCECE QetKis
because if you give one houra day to growth AAMRINSAE— BRAC de 48S; XOCECE QetKis
because if you give one houra day to growth AMR SAE — BTR MIC dwe 48S, XOCECE QetKis
because if you give one houra day to growth AAMRUNSAE— BTR AIC de 48S, XOCECE QRtKis
to purpose to vision Binzer due #485; XOCECE BB
to purpose to vision Binzer de #55, XOCECE QetKis
to health to people to your future nT HERAT MINT trina dwe #3, XOCECE Qantas
to health to people to your future WT PERAT MINT trina de +S; XOCECE QetKis
to health to people to your future WT PERAT MINT trina dwe 4S, MOCECE QetKis
one year from now de 44S; XOCECE QetKis
you'll be living a life you once only imagined trast tne 248 Rise th dwe #83, XOCECE QetKis
you'll be living a life you once only imagined iret e AB Rises EG de 48S, XOCECE Q RARE
so Start today FRU RFPS dwe #48; XOCECE BB
not because it's CaS but because it's worth It FERASRTEAAS de 48S, XOCECE Q RARE
not because it's CaS but because it's worth It FERASRTEANIS dwe +S, XOCECE Q RARE
not because it's CaS but because it's worth It FERNS RTEAAIES de 48S; XOCECE Q RARE
one hour one decision one NeW you —w\BI—Piae—teanniin dss #4 S:XOCECE ARE
one hour one decision one NeW you —v)\B— Piet eaten de 48S, XOCECE Q RARE
one hour one decision one NeW you —v)\B— Preteen des 48S, XOCECE Q satis
let that be your Story ikea SS de 48S, XOCECE Q RARE
#38S: XOCECE RAE AMES AMES ce
#9 S: XOCECE RAS AMES AMES dws
#9 S: XOCECE RAS AMES AMES He